Guide to the Gay Cable Network Archives, 1982-2001 MSS.231
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series X: Gay USA
  - 1993 Vol. XI
    - Gay USA, Vol. XI, Episode No. 2 [Air date: 1/7/1993], January 1993; ID: 231.0123 (Box 8, Media ID: 231.0123)
      6. "Cooking with Love": Michelle Levin, Nutrition Intern with God's Love We Deliver (GLWD), interviews Vivica Kraak, MS, RD, HIV Nutrition Specialist with GLWD, regarding healthy fast food for people with AIDS.
      7. "Lavender Health": Frank Oldham Jr., Director of the Office of Gay and Lesbian Health Concerns, interviews [Per Wennick], Director of the Danish Broadcasting Corporation, regarding AIDS in Denmark. Includes footage of the AIDS-themed remake of a Hans Christian Anderson fairy tale ["The Princess and the Condom"], a video "You can't catch AIDS from a swimming pool", and a clip from a more serious and informative AIDS program.
      8. "Naming Names": Donald Suggs, of the Gay and Lesbian Alliance Against Defamation (GLAAD) NY, discusses Mayor David Dinkins' executive orders regarding domestic partner benefits.
      9. Footage of Hon. David Dinkins, Mayor of NYC, at his domestic partner press conference on January 7, 1993.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XI, Episode No. 3 [Air date: 1/14/1993], January 1993; ID: 231.0124 (Box 8, Media ID: 231.0124)
    - Gay USA, Vol. XI, Episode No. 4 [Air date: 1/21/1993], January 1993; ID: 231.0125 (Box 8, Media ID: 231.0125)
      1. Andy Humm and Lee Sharmat discuss recent general events that relate to the LGBT community. Includes footage of Jerrold Nadler, member of Congress, discussing a gay rights bill.
      2. Footage of benefit for Gay Games IV. Includes Lee Sharmat interviewing Robby Brown, Co-Chair of Gay Games IV, and James Dale, who was thrown out of the Boy Scouts of America for being gay.
      3. Interview: Father Bernard Lynch, openly gay priest and author, regarding his personal story and his book "A Priest on Trial".
      4. "Lavender Health": Sean Dwyer, Associate Director of the Office of Gay and Lesbian Health Concerns, interviews Geoff Moore, Director of Education and Outreach for Body Positive, regarding the expanded definition of AIDS.
      5. "Naming Names": Cathay Che, of the Gay and Lesbian Alliance Against Defamation (GLAAD) NY, discusses gay rights measures in Colorado and the Colorado boycott.
      6. Footage of the inauguration of President Bill Clinton. Includes footage of Maya Angelou, writer and poet; Steve Guttenberg, actor; Rue McClanahan, actress; [Lisa Strongin], President of the Lesbian and Gay Bands of America.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XI, Episode No. 5 [Air date: 1/28/1993], January 1993; ID: 231.0126 (Box 8, Media ID: 231.0126)
    - Gay USA, Vol. XI, Episode No. 6 [Air date: 2/4/1993], February 1993; ID: 231.0127 (Box 8, Media ID: 231.0127)
    - Gay USA, Vol. XI, Episode No. 7 [Air date: 2/11/1993], February 1993; ID: 231.0128 (Box 8, Media ID: 231.0128)
      2. Footage of ACTUP demonstration at Hoffman-La Roche Plant in New Jersey on February 9, 1993. Includes Lou Maletta interviewing Barbara Hughs, Lawyer for ACTUP.
      COMMERCIAL: [Dr. Alan Tenenbaum], Psychotherapist, encourages viewers to call.
      3. Interview: Dick Dadey, [Executive Director] of the Empire State Pride Agenda, discusses political issues that affect the LGBT community. Includes NY1 footage of [Congressional] hearings with Major Owens, US Congressman, and Dov Hikind, anti-gay NYS Assembly Member. Also includes footage of Pat Robertson, "Professional Bigot", discussing bigotry.
      4. Lee Sharmat, the new Gay Games headquarters, interviews Orlando Diaz, [athlete]; Dan Baker, Gay Games Board Member; and Jay Hill, Executive Director of the Gay Games.
      5. Footage of Gay Games IV benefit at Splash. Includes Lee Sharmat interviewing Mary McFadden, fashion designer; Larry Kramer, [playwright and activist]; and employees of various bars.
      6. Human Rights Campaign Fund (HRCF) "Capitol Hill Update": Gregory King interviews Steve Smith, Research Director for HRCF, regarding the travel ban on people who are HIV-positive.
      COMMERCIAL: Dr. [Alan Tenenbaum], Psychotherapist, encourages viewers to call.
      7. "Naming Names": Cathay Che, of the Gay and Lesbian Alliance Against Defamation (GLAAD) NY, discusses recent NY Post cartoons by [Sean Delonas].
      8. "Lavender Health": Gregory Broyles, Director of the [Men of Color AIDS Prevention (MOCA)], interviews Vernon deJones and Paul Darling, regarding their personal experiences as members of the older black gay community.
      9. Clip of music video "Made for You" by Phoebe Legere
    - Gay USA, Vol. XI, Episode No. 8 [Air date: 2/18/1993], February 1993; ID: 231.0129 (Box 9, Media ID: 231.0129)
      2. Interview: Dick Dadey, [Executive Director] of the Empire State Pride Agenda, discusses a gay rights bill.
      3. Lee Sharmat interviews Nora Gibbons, gay bashing victim, regarding her attack.
      4. Lou Maletta interviews Gilles Mesrobian, Executive Director of Miracle House, and Suzanne E. Keller, Client Services Manager for Miracle House, regarding their organization's functions.
      5. Footage of Valentine's Day event in Bryant Park by the Lesbian Avengers celebrating the relationship between Gertrude Stein and Alice B. Toklas.
      6. "The Roving Camera": [John Calendo] introduces film clips of "great gay love scenes". Includes footage from "If…" (1968), "Desert Hearts" (1985), "Caged" (1950), and "[The] Boys in the Band" (1970).
      7. "Naming Names": Donald Suggs, of the Gay and Lesbian Alliance Against Defamation (GLAAD) NY, discusses domestic partnerships.
      8. Footage of event in Times Square regarding Marky Mark [Mark Wahlberg]'s anti-gay, violent history. Includes footage of David Nahmod, GCN Correspondent; Donald Suggs, of the Gay and Lesbian Alliance Against Defamation (GLAAD) NY; Dick Scott, Marky Mark's manager; Cathay Che, of the Gay and Lesbian Alliance Against Defamation (GLAAD) NY; and Maureen Burnley, of the NYC Gay and Lesbian Anti-Violence Project.
      COMMERCIAL: Homo Xtra
      9. "Lavender Health": Gregory Broyles, Director of the [Men of Color AIDS Prevention (MOCA)], and Yvette Burton, Director of the Lesbian Health Project, discuss the life and recent death of activist Craig G. Harris. Includes footage of Harris, and of people affected by Harris.
      10. Footage of Ann Northrop, Executive Director of the Gay and Lesbian Emergency Media Campaign, discussing her organization's response to the religious right's video "The Gay Agenda". Includes clip of the Gay and Lesbian Emergency Media Campaign video "Hate, Lies, & Videotape".
      11. Tim McCarthy interviews Stephen J. Smith, of ACTUP D.C., Inc., regarding changes in the structure of ACTUP.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XI, Episode No. 9 [Air date: 2/25/1993], February 1993; ID: 231.0130 (Box 9, Media ID: 231.0130)
      2. Interview: Joe Nicholson, Medicine and Sciences Editor of NY Post, discusses sex clubs and AIDS in NYC.
      3. Lou Maletta interviews Patricia Arias and Maribel Diaz, NY Police Officers, regarding the recruitment of minorities, including gays and lesbians, to the NY police force.
      4. Peter Levasseur, GCN Correspondent, interviews Danny Leonard, gay club owner in North Carolina, regarding his establishment
      5. "The Lambda Report" Denver, Colorado: Tiffany DiBlasil discusses the Colorado boycott. Includes footage of Mo Siegel, of Celestial Seasonings, and Terry Schleder, of Boycott Colorado.
      6. "Naming Names": Cathay Che, of the Gay and Lesbian Alliance Against Defamation (GLAAD) NY, discusses anti-gay music lyrics by Brand Nubian.
      7. Human Rights Campaign Fund (HRCF) "Capitol Hill Update": Gregory King interviews Tony Cheek, West Coast Regional Representative for HRCF, regarding the [SpeakOut]program.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XI, Episode No. 10 [Air date: 3/4/1993], March 1993; ID: 231.0131 (Box 9, Media ID: 231.0131)
      2. Lou Maletta interviews 'Eric and Douglas' regarding their newly recognized domestic partnership.
      3. Interview: Gabriel Rotello, NY Newsday Columnist, discusses a study of HIV from San Francisco.
      4. "The Lambda Report" Denver, Colorado: [Devin-Michael Morrisson] and David Medina discuss the Colorado boycott and political issues that affect the LGBT community.
      5. Footage of Irish Lesbian and Gay Organization (ILGO) press conference in response to a recent ruling regarding the exclusion of gays and lesbians from the St. Patrick's Day parade. Includes footage of Anne Maguire, [Eileen Clancy], and Paul O'Dwyer, all of ILGO.
      6. Lee Sharmat interviews Laurie Fierstein, [Miss USA 1991], regarding her bodybuilding.
      7. "Lavender Health": Frank Oldham Jr., Director of the Office of Gay and Lesbian Health Concerns, interviews Marjorie Hill, NYC Mayor Dinkins' Liaison to the gay and lesbian community, regarding her stepping down from her Liaison position.
      8. "Naming Names": Donald Suggs, of the Gay and Lesbian Alliance Against Defamation (GLAAD) NY, discusses a recent Channel 3 investigation of the North American Man/Boy Love Association (NAMBLA).
      9. Interview: 'Andy', owner of sex club Prism Gallery, discusses sex club regulations and proposed regulation changes.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XI, Episode No. 11 [Air date: 3/11/1993], March 1993; ID: 231.0132 (Box 9, Media ID: 231.0132)
      2. Footage of the Empire State Pride Agenda's Night of 100 Parties. Includes Lee Sharmat interviewing Valerie Gamache, Co-Chair of the Night of 100 Parties; Dick Dadey, [Executive Director] of the Empire State Pride Agenda; and Deborah Glick, NYS Assembly Member. Also includes Andy Humm interviewing David Straw, Co-Chair of the Night of 100 Parties; [Laurie Linton], Vice Chair of Empire State Pride Agenda; and [Allen Burnstein], organizer of the Liberty Tree.
      3. Lou Maletta interviews Billy Hileman, Nadine Smith, and 'Scout', National Co-Chairs of the March on Washington 1993, regarding the upcoming March.
      4. Interview: Raul Llorens and Mimi Plevin-Foust, Co-Producers of "Wide Time: Surviving AIDS", discuss their film. Includes film footage.
      5. Footage of benefit for the Gay and Lesbian Community Center. Includes Lee Sharmat interviewing Richard Burns, Executive Director of the Gay and Lesbian Community Center.
      6. Footage of Bill Baumer, founder of "Out the Window" comedy troupe, performing his own piece "Irish Eyes".
      7. "Naming Names": Cathay Che, of the Gay and Lesbian Alliance Against Defamation (GLAAD) NY, discusses a recent article in the NY Times by [Jeffrey Schmalz].
      8. "Lavender Health": Frank Oldham Jr., Director of the Office of Gay and Lesbian Health Concerns, interviews Marjorie Hill, NYC Mayor Dinkins' Liaison to the gay and lesbian community, regarding her stepping down from her Liaison position.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XI, Episode No. 12 [Air date: 3/18/1993], March 1993; ID: 231.0133 (Box 9, Media ID: 231.0133)
      1. Footage of the St. Patrick's Day Parade and protest by the Irish Lesbian and Gay Organization (ILGO). Includes footage of Brendan Fay and Paul O'Dwyer, of ILGO; Tom Duane, NYC Councilman; Roy Innis, Mayoral Candidate for NYC; Jack Hale, Lawyer for AOH [Ancient Order of Hibernians] and Mary Cummings; and Commissioner [Raymond] Kelly, NYC Police Chief.
      2. Interview: Donald Barr, of Gay and Lesbian Catholics of St. Paul the Apostle Church, discusses accepting the Irish Lesbian and Gay Organization (ILGO).
      3. Footage of Brendan Fay and Paul O'Dwyer, of ILGO, at [St. Paul the Apostle Church].
      4. Footage of Irish Lesbian and Gay Organization (ILGO) [press conference]. Includes footage of Anne Maguire and Paul O'Dwyer.
      5. Footage of the Gay and Lesbian Anti-Violence Project (AVP) press conference. Includes footage of Rudolph Giuliani, former US Attorney; Matt Foreman, Executive Director of the Gay and Lesbian Anti-Violence Project; and [Chris Pennock], victim of bias related violence
      6. Lou Maletta interviews Joe Stefan, former member of the US Navy, and Marc Wolinsky, Stefan's lawyer, regarding gays in the military.
      7. Footage of Mary C. Dunlap, Keynote Speaker, Teacher of Law, discussing political issues that affect the LGBT community at [the Lesbian and Gay Lawyers awards ceremony].
      8. "Lavender Health": Kevin Cathcart, Executive Director of the Lambda Legal Defense and Education Fund, introduces Paula Ettelbrick, who discusses leaving her position as Legal Director of Lambda Legal Defense and Education Fund. Includes Ellen Zaltzberg, of the Office of Gay and Lesbian Health Concerns, interviewing Paula Ettelbrick.
      9. Human Rights Campaign Fund (HRCF) "Capitol Hill Update": Gregory King interviews Tom Swift, National Canvas Manager of Speak Out for HRCF, regarding the Speak Out program.
      10. "Naming Names": Lisa Graziano, of the Gay and Lesbian Alliance Against Defamation (GLAAD) NY, discusses recent advertisements by Banana Republic that target lesbian consumers.
      11. Interview: Glenn Sheridan, Delegate of the NY March on Washington, and Carla Rabinowitz, Media Coordinator of the NY March on Washington, discuss the upcoming march.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XI, Episode No. 13 [Air date: 3/25/1993], March 1993; ID: 231.0134 (Box 9, Media ID: 231.0134)
      2. "The Lambda Report" Denver, Colorado: David Medina discusses Amendment 2. Includes footage of Gregory Walta, of Come Together Colorado; Suzanne Pharr, of Women's Project; Scott Nakagawa, of Oregon Citizens Alliance
      3. Footage of demonstration against Time Warner's [potential] elimination of public and leased access television. Includes footage of Dave Channon, Public Access [Producer] with Volcanic Video; Manny Manhattan, Public Access [Producer]; Rick X, Public Access [Producer] with Closet Case Show
      4. Lee Sharmat interviews Pat Hayes, Candidate for School Board District 24, regarding the Children of the Rainbow controversy.
      5. Danny Dromm, Co-Chair of Queens Pride, and Wendy Moscow, Outreach Chairperson for Queens Pride, discuss the first annual gay pride parade in Queens.
      6. Michael Petrelis and Michael Singerman, of Queer Nation D.C., discuss the murder of Navy seaman Allen Schindler, who was killed for being gay.
      7. Interview: Sam Ciccone, Co-Founder of the Gay Officers Action League (GOAL), and Christine Quinn, Chief of Staff for Tom Duane, discuss the arrests of gays and lesbians at the St. Patrick's Day parade.
      8. "Naming Names": Ellen Carton, Executive Director of the Gay and Lesbian Alliance Against Defamation (GLAAD) NY, discusses the film "Lost Language of Cranes" and asks viewers to encourage Blockbuster to carry the film. Includes film footage.
      9. Human Rights Campaign Fund (HRCF) "Capitol Hill Update": Gregory King interviews 'Scout', Co-Chair of the March on Washington, and Pat Hussain, Executive Committee Member of the March on Washington, regarding the upcoming march.
      10. "Lavender Health": Frank Oldham Jr., Director of the Office of Lesbian and Gay Health Concerns, interviews Richard M. Tagle, Project Director of the Gay and Bisexual Men of Color HIV Prevention Needs Assessment Project for the United States Conference of Mayors, regarding the Project.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XI, Episode No. 14 [Air date: 4/1/1993], April 1993; ID: 231.0135 (Box 9, Media ID: 231.0135)
      1. Andy Humm and Lee Sharmat discuss recent general events that relate to the LGBT community. Includes footage of Andy Humm interviewing Deborah Glick, NYS Assembly Member, regarding a lesbian and gay rights bill.
      2. Footage of the Gay and Lesbian Independent Democrats (GLID) mayoral forum at the Community Center. Includes footage of David Dinkins, Mayor of NYC; Andrew Stein, NYC Council President; and Matt Foreman, Executive Director of the Gay and Lesbian Anti-Violence Project (AVP).
      3. Glenn Sheridan, National Delegate to the March on Washington, and Bruce Fagin, Media Coordinator of the NY Committee for the March [on Washington], discuss the upcoming march.
      4. Lou Maletta interviews Michael Callen, activist and musician, regarding his 2-CD album "Legacy" and his activist work. Includes performance footage.
      5. Footage of the 4th annual GLAAD Media Awards. Includes footage of Phil Donahue, talk show host; Ellen Carton, Executive Director of the Gay and Lesbian Alliance Against Defamation (GLAAD) NY; Tony Randall, host [and actor]; Liz Smith, columnist; Donald Suggs, of GLAAD NY; Barbara Walters, TV host; David Sloan, Producer for "20/20"; Anna Quindlen, journalist; Kate Clinton, comedienne; Hendrich Hertzberg, [journalist] at The New Yorker; William Finn, [composer of] "Falsettos"; Jeffrey Schmalz, [journalist for] the NY Times; and Vivian Shapiro, of the NYC Commission on Human Rights. Also includes television clip of "One Life to Live".
      6. Footage of forum ["Operation Lift the Ban"]. Includes footage of Tom Stoddard, Head of Campaign for Military Service; Dr. James A. Forbes, Senior Minister at Riverside Church; Joseph Steffan, who was discharged from [the U.S. Naval Academy in] Annapolis; and Lou Maletta interviewing Gloria Steinem, head of the Ms. Foundation.
      7. Footage of the Night of 1000 Gowns. Includes footage of Empress Saleen, Empress VI of New York; Empress Razor Sharp, Chairman of Board [of the] Imperial Court; Coco La Chine, Crown Princess Royale; and Empress I Sybil, the Atlas Empress.
      8. "Lavender Health": Frank Oldham Jr., Director of the Office of Lesbian and Gay Health Concerns, interviews Richard M. Tagle, Project Director of the Gay and Bisexual Men of Color HIV Prevention Needs Assessment Project for the United States Conference of Mayors, regarding the Project.
      9. "Naming Names": Chiqui Cartagena, of the Gay and Lesbian Alliance Against Defamation (GLAAD) NY, discusses a recent article in Good Housekeeping regarding family values.
      10. GLAAD NY & Genre Magazine ad: "Gay USO at USA" event to lift the ban on gays in the military
      11. Additional footage of the Night of 1000 Gowns.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XI, Episode No. 15 [Air date: 4/8/1993], April 1993; ID: 231.0136 (Box 9, Media ID: 231.0136)
      2. Glenn Sheridan, Delegate to the March on Washington, and Tony Frankenberg, of the Steering Committee for the March on Washington, discuss the upcoming march.
      3. Carla Rabinowitz, of the Steering Committee for the March on Washington, promotes Lucie Blue Tremblay, musician, who will sing at a benefit for the March.
      COMMERCIAL: 1993 March on Washington
      4. Interview: Arthur Strickler, Past Chair of Board for CBST [Congregation Beit Simchat Torah], gay and lesbian synagogue, discusses the Salute to Israel Day Parade.
      5. Interview: Jon David Nalley, Candidate for School Board District 2, discusses the upcoming school board election.
      6. Interview: Jim Levin, gay activist and attorney, and Paul Shechtman, Counsel to Manhattan District Attorney Robert Morgenthau, discuss gay male harassment and arrests in public restrooms.
      7. Footage of Senate hearing regarding lesbians and gays in the military. Includes footage of Dan Coats, Republican Senator from Indiana; [Dr. Margarethe Cammermeyer], former colonel with the US military
      8. Human Rights Campaign Fund (HRCF) "Capitol Hill Update": Gregory King interviews Bert Wylen, host of ["Gaydreams"] radio program, regarding lesbians and gays in the military.
      9. "Lavender Health": Frank Oldham Jr., Director of the Office of Gay and Lesbian Health Concerns, interviews Tom Duane, NYC Council Member, regarding health issues that affect the LGBT community.
      10. "Naming Names": Donald Suggs, of the Gay and Lesbian Alliance Against Defamation (GLAAD) NY, discusses the gay-themed comic strip "For Better or For Worse".
    - Gay USA, Vol. XI, Episode No. 16 [Air date: 4/15/1993], April 1993; ID: 231.0137 (Box 9, Media ID: 231.0137)
      2. Interview: Frank Oldham Jr., gay activist, discusses issues of sex and race in the LGBT community.
      3. Interview: Crae Pridgen, survivor of anti-gay attack by US Marines, discusses his attack.
      4. GCN Sports: Footage of Lee Sharmat and Orlando Diaz at the first annual Bonnet races of Team New York Aquatics. Includes footage of Charles Carson, of Team New York Aquatics.
      5. Glenn Sheridan, Delegate for the March on Washington, and Don Grosso, Fundraising Coordinator for the March on Washington, discuss the upcoming march.
      6. Human Rights Campaign Fund (HRCF) "Capitol Hill Update": Gregory King interviews Terry Beswick, AIDS Research Policy Analyst for HRCF, regarding AIDS-related issues coming up in Congress.
      7. "Naming Names": Donald Suggs, of the Gay and Lesbian Alliance Against Defamation (GLAAD) NY, discusses a recent article in Redbook regarding lesbians and gays in college.
      8. Footage of the swearing in of Judge Richard Failla from December 1, 1988.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XI, Episode No. 17 [Air date: 4/22/1993], April 1993; ID: 231.0138 (Box 9, Media ID: 231.0138)
      1. Andy Humm and Lee Sharmat discuss recent general events that relate to the LGBT community. Includes NBC News clip of "Clinton and Gays", which includes footage of Tom Stoddard, [Head] of the Campaign for Military Service, and Tori Osborn, of the National Gay and Lesbian Task Force.
      2. Footage of press conference regarding the new classification of hate crimes, which now includes people with disabilities or AIDS. Includes footage of Hon. David Dinkins, Mayor of NYC; Raymond Kelly, Commissioner of the NYC Police Department; and Matt Foreman, Executive Director of the Gay and Lesbian Anti-Violence Project.
      3. Footage of "March for Truth" in District 24 of Queens, NY.
      4. Glenn Sheridan, of the March on Washington, and Michelle Eason, Transport Coordinator for the March on Washington, discuss the upcoming march.
      COMMERCIAL: March on Washington 1993
      5. Andy Humm and Lee Sharmat introduce the endorsements from School PAC regarding the upcoming NYC school board elections.
      6. [Phyllis Lutsky and Kelly Cogswell], of the Lesbian Avengers, discuss the upcoming Dyke March to the White House.
      7. Interview: Gabriel Rotello, NY Newsday Columnist, discusses a NY Times article regarding the percentage of people who identify as homosexual.
      8. "Naming Names": Cathay Che, of the Gay and Lesbian Alliance Against Defamation (GLAAD) NY, discusses a NY Times article regarding the percentage of people who identify as homosexual.
      9. "Lavender Health": Frank Oldham Jr., Director of the Office of Gay and Lesbian Health Concerns, interviews Marjorie Hill, NYC Mayor Dinkins' Liaison to the gay and lesbian community, regarding political events that affect the LGBT community.
      10. Clip of music video for "I Melt with You" by Modern English.
      11. Clip of two men kissing with message "Get Used to It".
    - Gay USA, Vol. XI, Episode No. 18 [Air date: 4/29/1993], April 1993; ID: 231.0139 (Box 9, Media ID: 231.0139)
      1. Footage from the March on Washington of the candlelight vigil honoring gay and lesbian Holocaust victims.
      2. Footage from the March on Washington of the HRCF black tie dinner. Includes footage of Ted Kennedy, Democratic Senator from Massachusetts, and Dorothy Hodges, mother of hate crime victim Allen Schindler.
      3. Footage from the March on Washington of the Victory Fund brunch that honored lesbian and gay appointed officials. Includes footage of [James Carville], Clinton Campaign Strategist, and [Tim Mains], Mayoral Candidate for Rochester, NY.
      4. Footage from the March on Washington of "The Wedding; Interfaith Ceremony of Commitment".
      5. Footage from the March on Washington of Ken McPherson discussing the Harvey Milk Memorial design unveiling.